if you're feeling a palpable sexual
excitement in the air it's probably
because the vice presidential debate was
tonight oh there they Tim Kane and Mike
Pence otherwise known as white guy 37b
and white guy 55 c squared
up hang on that's Mr Belding and the dad
from that 70
show Jack will you please put up the
right photos no Jack that is Ned
Flanders in a bowl of rice please find
photos of VP candidates all right that's
better
uh
now since we were busy taping at the
time we didn't get to see the debate as
it happened so we're just assuming that
at some point harmonica Enthusiast Tim
Kane did a and duet with John
popper from Blues Traveler and that Mike
Pence revealed he's been a dummy
controlled by Jeff Dunham this entire
time either way Americans know next to
nothing about these two so comedians
what's a question they should have been
asked to get to the Core of these
storebrand white guys Louis Anderson
have you ever owned stock in Cracker
Barrel points points are you Cracker
Barrel Brendon Walsh uh what's your
favorite Jimmy Buffett song and you
can't say all of them yes points Martha
Kelly oh should 21st century American
women be allowed to get abortions or
just fake
boobs points
points